const Questions = {
    Math: [
        { question: "What is 64/8?" , options: ["8","0","4","2"], answer:"8"},
        { question: "What is the positive square root of 4 ?" , options: ["2","0","4","8"], answer:"2"},
        { question: "What is 9+10?" , options: ["21","19","90","900"], answer:"19"},
        { question: "What is the derivate of x?" , options: ["1","x","x^2","pi"], answer:"1"},
        { question: "What is 3*6" , options: ["18","0","99","9"], answer:"18"},
        { question: "What are the first 5 digits of pi?" , options: ["3.14157","3.14158","3.14159","3.14167"], answer:"3.14159"},
        { question: "What is 6%3 (modulo)?" , options: ["3","0","18","2"], answer:"0"},
        { question: "What is 9/0" , options: ["undeifned","0","9","negative infinity"], answer:"undeifned"},
        { question: "What is 3!" , options: ["6","3","2","1"], answer:"6"},
        { question: "What is X if 56=8x?" , options: ["8","7","56","32"], answer:"7"},
    ],

    Science:

    History:

    Geography:

    English:

    Art:

    Music:

    Computer Science:

    PE:

};
